hi spring fans welcome to another super
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个超级
mikro edition of spring tips in which
mikro版的春季提示，其中
we're going to look at one or two
我们要看一两个
compelling new features in spring boot
spring boot 引人注目的新功能
to that to m1 now of course bring boot
当然现在要启动M1
2.2 is not yet GA but it's it's
2.2还不是通用航空，而是
certainly down the pike you know and you
当然是你知道的派克
can try it out already on the spring
可以在春天尝试一下
analyzer the much renewed much revamped
分析仪更新了很多，更新了很多
start out spring that IO experienced
从IO经历的春天开始
which I have here open in the browser
我在这里在浏览器中打开的
we're gonna build a application that
我们将构建一个应用程序
highlights some of the things that you
突出显示您的一些事情
can do to improve your performance
可以改善您的表现
experience when developing applications
开发应用程序的经验
with spring boot ok so we're gonna build
spring boot 好，所以我们要建立
an application that demonstrates that
演示该应用程序的应用程序
you can be both lazy and fast okay we're
你可以既懒又快，好吧，我们
gonna use an application I'm gonna build
将使用我要构建的应用程序
an application that uses the reactive
使用反应式的应用程序
web support for example reactive Hmong
网络支持，例如反应式苗族
would he be reactive web or is Lombok
他会是反应性网络还是龙目岛
why not
为什么不
maybe and we use the spring boot dev
也许，我们使用spring boot dev
tools and I think that's it that's
工具，我认为就是这样
probably enough we can you can add of
大概够了，我们可以添加
things of course but I'm just trying to
当然可以，但我只是想
demonstrate some concepts here so we're
在这里演示一些概念，所以我们
going to do is we have an application
要做的是我们有一个应用程序
we're gonna open the zip file open it up
我们将打开zip文件将其打开
in our IDE it doesn't all that much
在我们的IDE中并没有那么多
matter what I do you use I'm gonna be
不管我用什么我都会
using IntelliJ but again most of this
使用IntelliJ，但这又是大多数
applies to other IDs as well and we're
同样适用于其他ID，我们
different I'll point out the differences
我会指出不同之处
alright so we've got this new project
好了，所以我们有了这个新项目
and before we get too far down the way
在我们走得太远之前
I'm going to set up a property here in
我要在这里建立一个物业
our public static void main application
我们的公共静态无效主应用程序
that's new in spring mood 2.2 so system
这是春季心情2.2中的新功能
dot sets property spring dot mean dot
点集属性弹簧点均值点
lazy initialization and I'm gonna set
延迟初始化，我要开始了
this to be false
这是错误的
okay and that's but it is false by
好的，那是错误的，
default but I want to make sure we
默认，但我想确保我们
understand what it's what it's doing I'm
了解我在做什么
gonna comment this stuff out so it's
要评论这个东西，所以
gonna get rid of the web flux and the
将摆脱网通量和
monger to be reactive stuff so we have
贩子是反应性的东西，所以我们有
kind of a baseline for what it looks
外观的基准
like of course I need to bring in spring
就像我当然要带春天
boot itself now that those are now that
现在启动自己，那些现在是
know now that it's no longer a
现在知道它不再是
transitive dependency so I'll bring in
传递依赖，因此我将引入
spring boot starter and with that I'll
Spring Boot Starter，然后我会
have everything I want now I'm gonna
现在拥有我想要的一切
also add one thing here I'm going to add
在这里还要添加​​一件事
environment
环境
- no verify ok this is a setting that
-不验证，确定这是
I think as sort of a bygone thing from
我认为这是过去的事情
the era of applets which makes no sense
小程序的时代没有意义
in the modern to reserved side
在现代到保留的一面
continuously integrated continuously
不断整合
built continuously packaged continually
持续建造，持续包装
delivered microservices the world of the
提供微服务的世界
server-side Java and scape ok so with
服务器端Java和scape也可以
that let's go ahead and start this first
让我们继续并首先开始
time compiling all right so it's point
时间编译没事，这很重要
five seven three seconds I'm gonna
我要五七三秒
restart it a few times just to get a
重新启动几次只是为了
sort of running sense of what the
那种什么的奔跑感
numbers are Oh point five oh seven point
数字是五点哦七点
five one three point five one two
五一三分五一二
Oh point five or eight etc so half a
哦，五点或八点等等，半点
second right a little bit less than a
第二个权利比一个少
little bit more than a half a second
超过半秒
okay now bring in the dependencies here
好吧，现在在这里引入依赖
our web server our data accessed here
我们的网络服务器，我们的数据在这里访问
and just to be fair and let's start that
公平地说，让我们开始吧
[Music]
[音乐]
all right so one point 269 restart again
好的，所以一点269重新启动
one point two to five
一分二到五分
1.26
1.26
Oh already in use what is that
哦，已经在使用那是什么
okay 1.2 69
好1.2 69
one point two four seven so 1.25 isch is
一分二四七所以1.25 isch
that fair I think as you know it's less
那公平，我想你知道
than one point three eight certainly now
现在肯定比一分三八
let's try true okay so spring main lazy
让我们尝试真正的好吧，所以春季主要懒惰
initialization is true and see what that
初始化是正确的，看看有什么
gives us point eight six eight
给我们点八六八
point eight seven eight
点八七八
Oh point eight seven nine
喔点八七九
okay point 907 so you can see it's
好点907，所以您可以看到
between point eight and point nine I
在八点和九点之间
think is pretty fair to say you can
认为可以公平地说
expect that now
现在期待
I like the lazy initialization what
我喜欢延迟初始化什么
that's doing is it's lazy the
这样做是在偷懒
initializing beans as it's as though you
初始化bean，就好像您
had added at lazy to your beans and in
懒惰地添加到您的豆子中
particular since we have a lot of auto
特别是因为我们有很多汽车
configuration that gets created that you
您创建的配置
may not use or may not be involved those
可能不使用或可能不参与
things get the initialization of those
事情得到那些的初始化
things get deferred until when you
事情推迟到你
actually need them are there some things
实际需要他们有一些东西
you should know about yes if you have a
如果你有一个，你应该知道是的
bean that has a constructor and you're
有一个构造函数的bean，
expecting as a side effect of that
期望作为一个副作用
constructor to have some effect visible
构造函数具有可见的效果
in the application at the startup time
在启动时在应用程序中
well that doesn't happen anymore right
好吧，这不再发生了
those beans that have constructor logic
那些具有构造函数逻辑的bean
that constructor doesn't get called
该构造函数不会被调用
until the bean is being used it doesn't
直到豆被使用，它才被使用
get called at first right you have to
首先要打电话给你
actually invoke it now if you have an
如果您有一个
application listener or an event
应用程序侦听器或事件
listener or whatever for for an event
侦听器或用于事件的任何东西
for example application started event or
例如应用程序启动事件或
you know or application ready event
您知道或应用程序就绪事件
rather or something like that then yeah
还是那样的话
that will be called but simple
那将被称为但简单
construction all that stuff gets
建设所有东西得到
deferred until when you first use the
推迟到您第一次使用
object now I don't think most people
现在反对，我不认为大多数人
gonna have that problem if using a
如果使用
command line run or an application
命令行运行或应用程序
winner those will be invoked at the
获胜者将在
right time but otherwise this deferred
合适的时间，但否则推迟了
to to first use now my next favorite
首先要使用我的下一个收藏夹
feature is something called dev tools so
功能就是所谓的开发工具
that's before I do this I'm gonna
那是在我做这个之前
restart the application using debug mode
使用调试模式重新启动应用程序
so I'm restarting okay I'm stopping the
所以我要重启，然后停止
application and restarting remember the
应用程序并重新启动请记住
debug mode is slightly slower then
调试模式会稍微慢一些
running in your IDE usually okay but now
通常可以在您的IDE中运行，但是现在
that it's running in debug mode I'm
它正在调试模式下运行
gonna do router function server response
将做路由器功能服务器响应
routes I'm just gonna create a simple
我将要创建的简单路线
endpoint here just to demonstrate the
这里的端点只是为了演示
idea request predicates dot get high
想法请求谓词点变高
okay request okay body or save buddy
好吧，请问好身体或保存好友
hello world alright so I'm just building
你好，世界好，所以我正在建造
a simple functional reactive endpoint
一个简单的功能性反应终点
here you've seen me do this a million
在这里你已经看到我做到了这一百万
and a half times everyone
每个人半倍
okay now I'm gonna instead of restarting
好吧，我现在要重启
the application which is the natural
自然的应用
instinct normally if you want to start
如果你想开始，通常是本能的
it you hit control R if you do drawn the
如果您确实绘制了
max there's a button on the top of your
最大，您的顶部有一个按钮
smart Keyboard a smart bar whatever they
智能键盘智能酒吧，无论他们
can press but I'm not gonna run it
可以按，但我不会运行
instead I'm gonna just build it I'm
取而代之的是我要建立它
gonna I'm gonna just compile it now this
我要现在编译它
is a little bit of an awkward thing to
有点尴尬
do if you're if you're used to just
如果你习惯了
running it inside of your ID but here
在您的ID内运行它，但是在这里
I'm just gonna build it which is the
我只是要建造它
there's a hammer icon at the top of my
我的顶部有一个锤子图标
IDE and you can see it says point here
IDE，您可以看到它指向此处
0.23 seconds okay so now localhost hi
0.23秒还可以，所以现在localhost hi
and there's my my endpoint okay so now
我的终点站好了，所以现在
let's say I want to change this to have
假设我想更改此设置
more exclamation marks now with extra
现在有了更多的感叹号
exclamation marks all for the low low
感叹号全部为低低
low low price of just one exclamation
低价低价而已
mark is on now I'm gonna clear my
马克在现在我要清除我的
console here we go
控制台我们去
clear it all and I'm gonna read compile
清除所有内容，我将阅读编译
but not rerun or I think I did rerun it
但不重新运行，或者我认为我确实重新运行过
actually whoops I hit the wrong button
其实我打错了按钮
darn it
该死
let me try that again we're gonna add
让我再试一次，我们要添加
Hodor right this is the Game of Thrones
霍多尔（Wodor），这是权力的游戏
version of hello world and now I'm not
世界的版本，现在我不是
gonna restarted I'm just gonna recompile
要重新启动，我要重新编译
but let me before I do this okay so
但是在我做这个之前先让我
clear all and then recompile there we go
清除所有内容，然后重新编译
so you can see the change was visible
这样您就可以看到更改是可见的
there in point three nine three seconds
大约三九三秒
let me move down to one exclamation mark
让我下降到一个感叹号
like this I'm gonna recompile and then
这样我要重新编译然后
you can see that that is now visible
您可以看到现在可见
already in point two three nine seconds
已经在第二，三，九秒
so I go back to the browser refresh
所以我回到浏览器刷新
there it is
在那里
so with with these features it's super
所以有了这些功能，它超级好
trivial to like to you know greatly
不容易喜欢你就知道
increase the start time free application
增加免费启动时间
to make development all that much more
进行更多的开发
fun and there's other things you can do
有趣，还有其他事情可以做
like for example I find that uh no
例如，我发现，嗯，不
verify help so this is actually a uh you
验证帮助，所以这实际上是您
know might be as much as 0.1 seconds
知道可能多达0.1秒
right it's a every little bit helps I
对，这对我有一点帮助
guess alright so I just wanted to
猜对了，所以我只想
demonstrate some of these features I
展示一些我的功能
hope you enjoyed them and as usual
希望你喜欢他们，像往常一样
thanks for watching and we'll see you
谢谢收看，我们见
next time
下次
[Music]
[音乐]
you
您